I have seen a lot of game of the year 2015 videos and they are all wrong
So I decided to make my own video the problem
Is that the only game? I play this entire year is City Skylines, so for all the other games. I just read the Wikipedia articles
Before I talk about my [top] three let's just denounce all the other video games that didn't make it
Here is my city it took seven hundred hours to make but I haven't built any
Hospitals because these griffith swats only pay 10% [packs]
Logically because this is the only game I played this entire year
It should be my game of the year no. I can't give my award to a clone
Yes
City Skylines is a shitty version of [atilla] total war you have to manage
Population [king] waters at fire to stop. They are so similar
I'm surprised creative assembly hasn't soon, but speaking of [city] seems my favorite hidden gem [of] this year is a little indie title called
Mass effect for the Expo live
But it's not my game of the year because the graphics are just not
Next-gen another exponent exclusive is Halo 5 first let me say that halo 5 is better than Halo 4 that shouldn't surprise
Anyone because [Halo] 4 is the worst game ever made and that's not an opinion
That's a fact Halo 5 supposedly has very good multiplayer
But the single-Player campaign is shorter than this video
I have yet to play it sadly because it's a Yankee
Exclusive well not really but it's next box 1 exclusive and exponents yet to be released in Europe. Oh wait
It has where's no one told Europeans 1 out of 10 speaking of short games the world record is held by Batman Arkham knight
Game is one minute long then closes itself if you hack it you get this 20 hour long easter [egg]
That should be 15 hours there are parts of this video game that would have been so much better
If there was just a screen that popped up and said a couple of hours later
My favorite swedish game this year was a romantic. Comedy game called what a Saturday
I think the international title is [soma] and was marketed as a our game
I don't know why I didn't find that scary. Maybe the true horror comes from the fact now
We have to wait forever for the next frictional game so much stays with you after you finished playing it, but so did bioshock
So maybe it's not because it has [a] great story. Maybe under water games you stay with you now can the game without?
[multiplayer] and they were stan on existent campaign be good
Sort of it's very pretty if you like nature just cos 3 is great
I don't I think they should purge all of this and build
57,000 shopping malls also driving is bad, but that's a good thing [because] you didn't expect driving to be bad
So it serves as a plot twist and complements the story another swedish game was the mad max game [I]
Got nothing there was one more swedish game, and it was the biggest one, but let's not talk about that [I]
Used to think Ea could do no wrong
Let's talk movies because this year there was a sequel we were all waiting for and on December 18th
They finally released Alvin and the Chipmunks 3 and it was a masterpiece
but it got massacred at the box office by the
Seventh movie of a series no one [cultured] has ever heard of the same thing happened to rise of the tomb Raider
Because of fallout 4 it only sold 17 copies, so I don't know what to tell you about this one
I think this lady is the protagonist and in the e3 trailer. I saw it had snow
Going to need a little bit more than that if I'm going to make it my game of the year speaking [of] movies
They seriously force. Teen nikola tesla. Also. There's like no banter in this entire game
Why would you put a game in England and not have any banter luckily this is the only game [set] in [Victorian], England
Assassin's Creed Arkham County is a game where you enslaved children, but it's the good kind of enslavement the one that benefits you
It's set in London and as a British cast the problem
Is that we already had an assassin's creed game with a British cast so the solution was to make them even more?
British both types of brits are here
We have the [lower-class] who is good at insulting and fighting
But we also have the posh brits then there's her who doesn't wear a tuxedo nor does. She shouted strangers
She is the worst kind of brit the normal kind completely ruins the game one out of ten luckily
This is the only game set in Victorian, England [I]
Guess [it's] not really set in Victorian, England
Not one is a japanese games you can tell from this doll, and the Japanese can't make video games
They only make talking simulators with kids you hope sacrifices themselves in the end
They don't make any real games like metal gear or dark souls my biggest problem with the Blood-Borne
Is that the story is not straightforward?
To get a full story you need to read item descriptions or more likely watch [Youtube] videos
This is a problem for people who are not sure how to read unlike the games I mentioned
metal gear
explains
Literally everything to you
except for the things you won't explain and dark souls doesn't even have a story you are supposed to make up your own story and
It's part of the fun also [Volpone] is too easy I go through the entire Wikipedia page without dying once
[metal] [Gear] [5] was published by Konami and
directed by hit a konami when he said he wanted to turn metal gear into a Sandbox game everyone thought he meant the
Genre in these games the enemy is always some shitty paramilitary. Why does the metal gear universe have all these eccentric?
paramilitaries with leaders with superpowers
One time I wish they would [just] walk up to a guy and why are you here and what are your super abilities?
Abilities were you talking about we just five guys bought some shots [things] got out of hand and now we have this experimental
Wmd, but I am disappointed that economic fired Konami [all] in all good game
And hit Konami Pr Department deserves all the awards he gets one out of ten
[all] Detail was developed by Toby Fox
But he represents himself as a dog so off to a bad start [the] big [problem] with on [tail]
Is that you don't have to kill anyone, but there's no reason not to it's just faster
Then I found out you can get a different ending by killing everything and then stuff didn't render
unfinished garbage
But I caved in and decided to play a mercy run and it was nothing special
Kind of annoying because there were several point throughout the game
I had to go out to the kitchen and cut onions lots and lots of onions
Onions of friendship a little problem with undertale is that the soundtrack is really really good and it cost every Youtube game
Musician to have a Mental breakdown
I
Have yet to play the witcher 3 because I heard that if you want the full experience
You have to be fluent in polish, so I can't review the witcher
But I can review the lingos Polish course [1] out of 10 so far
I know how to say curva and vodka and that's about
70% of the language in the game you play as this guy, and you're supposed to rescue this girl
And that's it eventually you make it to Scottish, scandinavia
And it's a cold shithole every time someone makes a scandinavian [place] [tall] with a cold shithole rest of the planet you guys are dicks
It took me 100 hours to finish. I expected 102 so clearly the game needs more
Polish needs More Polish I
Bought fallout 4 on day [1], but I mean, it's pretty good, but it's not
It's just not as good as runescape when I was killing ghouls I thought I could be doing this in Runescape
When I was entering the institute I thought I could be training fire-making right now another problem
Is [that] they don't say what they are supposed to say if you tell me there's [some] [mods]. I think you are misunderstanding
I want my character to walk around the Wasteland and say the word sarcastic the people you can kill the brotherhood of steel
So I'm recommending it. I would just like to inform everyone that this isn't my opinion
It's science, and if you disagree with this you are wrong
If you create a video game with the writing of dostoevsky and the directing of Kurosawa you get five nights at Freddy's 3
Snap three is very close to me because it was the final [game] [in] the series
For a couple of months [10] out of 10
Like I said I used to think that Ea could do no wrong and I was fucking right
Battlefront is the best goddamn star wars game ever made it's like being there and by there
I mean back in 2004 playing the original
Battlefront Battlefront is a goddamn masterpiece and the only reason you don't like it is because you [are] bad at it
Fuck you. Metacritic. Fuck you reddit fuck you dean video game community. Oh the game only has four maps
Yeah
well
So does the wit [-] you fucking hypocrite follow [four] more like [dogshit] for the witcher?
more like the [dogshit] sure on the tail more like already has way too many dog references [9] out of 10 and
the game of the year goes to
game of thrones
I haven't said video game once in this entire video the best thing about game of thrones is that when a new game of thrones
Episode comes out you know
There's new Silicon Valley episode also now that the series has gone past books. We have the upper hand now
We shall film the reaction of the book readers Glory to the TV watchers
But final words, I completely forgot call of duty, and that is the killing experience